seoreseller.com 2019-07-30

# SEOReseller Online Privacy Policy | SEOReseller

Our company, seoreseller.com, is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Online Privacy Statement regarding the privacy practices of our website found on www.seoreseller.com. Please note that this statement applies only to the collection and use of information obtained online and not to data gathered offline. By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy. When you visit our website, expect to be notified of the following:

  * The collection and use of identifiable personal information;
  * Information sharing and choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of personal information;
  * Online privacy protection for children;
  * How we protect personal information;
  * Links to other sites;
  * Notice of amendments;
  * Contacting us regarding personal information and privacy concerns.

### WEBSITE LOGIN AND “COOKIES”

The company owns the information collected at several different points on our website. We do not sell, share, or rent to other parties for ways or purposes not disclosed in this statement. The company collects personal and non-personal information in order to provide you with our services, including access to the website’s newsletter, marketing and for advertising purposes. Below are the types of information we collect and their description.

  1. Personal and demographic information. Details that can help us identify you may include name, address, telephone number, or email address.
  2. Cookies. These are small text data that enable you to sign in to our services and allow us to enhance your online experience. Commonly stored on your hard disk drive, these are records of your preferences and other data on your computer so as to save time by eliminating the need of repeatedly providing the same information during later visits. They cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. The use of the cookie does not link to any identifiable personal information while on our site. You may reject their use but your experience may be limited in some areas of our site. Our business partners including advertisers may also use cookies on our site. We have no access or control over such cookies.
  3. Log files. These are IP addresses that help us administer the site, evaluate trends, track user’s movement, and collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. They are not linked to identifiable personal information.

We may receive and collect personal information about you such as name, email address, behavior data etc. from third party sources given that they are authorized to share your information and we have the rights to use them.

### EMAIL ACCESS

The company can access your email once you provide your credentials. By providing your credentials, you are consenting to give us access to your emails for the purpose of sending emails on your behalf and storing replies to those emails.

We only access emails from contacts that you have added in our system. The company ensures its employee do not have access to the content of the emails, and all emails are encrypted. The company only aggregates statistical data about usage.

You have the right to opt-out of sharing your information anytime. To opt-out of advertising campaigns, please email us at marketing@seoreseller.com with your registered email account. We will remove you from all remarketing campaigns within 30 days of confirmation.

### GOOGLE ACCOUNT

You can log in, sign up and send email in SEOReseller using your Google/Gmail account. The App name used when you do these actions is “YourDashboard”.

We collect the following information:

  * Email address
  * Google ID

We keep this information as long as you keep your account with us. Upon deletion of your account, your data will be completely erased from our servers within 90 days.

We use this information to be able to create your account and contact you properly.

We also allow you to connect your Gmail/G Suite account for you to be able to send emails from your Gmail/Gsuite account from our CRM. This access will be revoked if you change your email sending settings or close your account.

### GOOGLE ANALYTICS DATA

We allow you to integrate your Google Analytics account with our platform for reporting purposes. We can also modify or create some settings on your behalf as well. We do not save any of your Google Analytics data.

### OWNERSHIP OF DATA

All data you entered in our platform belongs to you. You can request a complete export of your data anytime. Also, you can request a deletion of your account, that would entail a complete deletion of all your data within 3 (three) months.

### COMMUNICATION

The company shares aggregated demographic information with partners and advertisers. This type of anonymous data is collected for purposes of studying a group or category of services or users. The information is not linked to any personal data that can be identified with any individual person.

We work with other parties to assist us and provide specific services and, during these instances, we share name and contact details that are necessary for service provision. Our partners are not allowed to use identifiable personal information in any way other than the purpose of providing our listed services. Non-personal and identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

We may release identifiable personal information in compliance with the law to enforce our site policies, or to protect our, your, and other’s rights, property, or safety.

### SECURITY

In compliance with the requirements of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, the company does not knowingly intend to collect information from individuals 13 years of age or younger.

### YOUR RIGHT

The company maintains at all times administrative, technical, and physical safety measures to protect identifiable personal information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

### LINKING

Our website contains links to other sites for convenience and information. Our company is not responsible for the privacy policies in these sites. We advise that you review the privacy notices for the use of such sites.

### NOTIFICATION

Should the company decide to make material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you by posting a notice of such change at the site’s Homepage. Should the company decide to use identifiable personal information, we will notify you via electronic mail. You have the choice whether to let us use information in a different manner or not. The use of information follows the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### CONTACT US

Should you feel the company is not abiding by its declared privacy policy, please contact [info@seoreseller.com](mailto:info@seoreseller.com).
